hello everyone
today i had some time off and decided to
take you along on some adventures
since i moved here i've been teaching
myself to skate
i'm not very good at it but the frozen
lake is a wonderful place to practice
especially when there's a sprinkle of
new fallen snow over the ice
it doesn't let you gain too much speed
instead you can work
on your balance
[Music]
as you can see eiger was very excited to
be on the lake today
he first experienced the snow last year
when i brought him home as a puppy
and it has quickly become his favorite
[Music]
season
do
[Music]
did you know that if you light a candle
when you glimpse the first star in a
clear night sky
the kindly moon rabbit may just stop by
your home while you sleep
and sprinkle fairy dust on your forehead
filling your dreams with whimsy and
delight
at least when i was a child i was
definitely convinced that this would
happen
and i still love to light candles just
in case
[Music]
the next morning i woke up with the sun
and took a long walk with iger
i think that there are few joys more
deeply felt than a morning walk with a
beloved pet
it is one of my favorite parts of my day
i recently told luke that i was missing
my visits to the mountains
so he gave me some crystals that he had
found to remind me of the peaks
now obstructed by so much snow
these crystals probably look nothing
like the ones you find in shops
and that is because commercial crystals
have gone through a very rigorous
process of chemical cleaning
the end result is spectacular but i
personally enjoy these more natural
versions as well
they have their own unique type of
beauty
in a strange way these natural crystals
remind me to value my own imperfections
[Music]
it is so easy to compare our natural
selves with the flawless
imagery that we see in edited
photographs and advertisements
but those images like polished and cut
crystals
come from a labored process of changing
something from its natural state
to something different while i respect
that a lot of these images are art
i also am aware that much of what we see
in my culture is an advertisement
and while it may be beautiful it
sometimes omits the origin story that we
all have every little blemish is part of
our personal legend
just as each divet on the face of this
crystal is intrinsic to its formation
[Music]
you may not have noticed because i try
not to showcase it
but the tip of one of my fingers is
slightly malformed
this was due to an accident as a child
and i was deeply
self-conscious when i was much younger i
don't see it as something beautiful but
i now understand that it is part of my
story and i wouldn't want it any other
way
similarly by being biracial my features
are a combination of my ancestors
who come from very different parts of
the world if my eyes were bigger
my nose smaller i would lose the imprint
of their lives
their stories and their appearance i
would feel
less connected
[Music]
i hope that whoever you are you love
your naturally given features and learn
to embrace your imperfections
and see that things you may wish were
different are actually just part of your
legend
your origin story and the evidence of
the thousand lives that lived before you
[Music]
thank you for sharing a little bit of
this day with me
i will be thinking of you and i will see
you next week
you